In the library window, double-click to open the practice folder.
Find the C details folder.
Find the B Constructing and Shoot Practice folder.
In the file, choose Shoot Practice.
Or drag it to the 3D window.
Use the loop outline tool.
On the purple base line in the front, right-click and select the menu.
Select the cut and sew.
The front panel will be divided into two lines based on the selected line.
And the sewing line will automatically be created between two panels.
In the 2D window, use the adjustment panel tool.
Select the door panel.
In the sound editor, select the stretch.
In the fire window, use the 3D window.
To show the thickness of the door panel in the real sample,
you need to set the thickness of the hematopoietic.
In the library window, click on the tree.
Find the corresponding thickness at the bottom of the side of the mouse.
In the 2D window, select the door panel.
Find the thickness of the hematopoietic in the side of the mouse.
Enter the thickness of the tree.
In order to show the double-layer effect of the single-layer panel,
select the double-layer effect in the
button and select the outer layer of the colon.
Keep the colon straight to the top of the published panel.
In the 2D window, select the edit sewing line tool.
Select the sewing line of the pattern on the colon.
Press the delete button to delete the blurring.
Re-mix the blurring.
Note that one side is open, do not mix.
In the sound editor,
Change the blurring type to Tint.
After fire simulation, the blurring will be more even.
Fire simulation, apply the settings to 3D clothing.
In the object window, select the button.
In the operating editor, change the thickness of the button.
After fire simulation, apply the settings to 3D clothing.
In the effect editor, uh, about 40%, movie 3D is applied and 100% is created.
ник
How to scriptures
Can you wonder?
Tint
Closed!
Nuts!
Blurning?
Or else?
Another action!
Denhhg!